pageaday.com 2014-04-27

# Terms / Privacy - Page-A-Day

About

By using this site, you agree to the Privacy Policy of Workman Publishing. Workman Publishing reviews its Privacy Policy periodically, and reserves the right to modify, add, or remove portions of this Policy at any time. Please review this page from time to time, so that you will be aware of any changes. This Privacy Policy applies to all Websites produced and operated by Workman Publishing. For additional restrictions and regulations, please see the privacy policy of the site in question. If you want to communicate with us about our Policy, please email us at info@workman.com or write to us at:

 **Online Department  
Workman Publishing  
225 Varick Street  
New York, NY 10014-4381**

This site is owned and/or operated Workman Publishing, Inc. Please refer to our [Terms of Use](http://www.workman.com/about/terms/) for details on using or distributing some of the information available on this site.

Workman Publishing is committed to protecting the privacy and security of its online visitors. To assist us in this, Workman Publishing strongly advises monitoring the Internet use of children 13 years and younger.

What follows is a listing of sites owned or supported by Workman Publishing: [Workman.com](http://www.workman.com/)  PageADay.com, [BrainQuest.com](http://www.brainquest.com/);[1,000 Places To See Before You Die](http://1000places.com/); [The Mom 100](http://www.themom100.com/); [Workman’s Blue Plate Special](http://www.workman.com/ecookbook-club); [Artisan Cookbook Club](http://www.workman.com/artisanbooks/cookbook-club/); [Barbecue Bible](http://barbecuebible.com/); [Scanimation Books](http://scanimationbooks.com/); [1,000 Recordings To Hear Before You Die](http://www.1000recordings.com/); [The Cake Mix Doctor](http://www.cakemixdoctor.com/).

### Automatic Data Collection

When a visitor requests a page of information from a Website, information about the request is automatically stored in a log file. This information includes the Internet address of the computer making the request, the time and date of the request, the type of Web browser being used, and sometimes, the page from which the visitor is coming. The information does not contain the visitor's name or email address since the visitor's browser does not provide this information to the Web server.

Workman Publishing analyzes these log files to learn about how visitors are using the content of the site. This information is used to allocate resources effectively and improve the content of our site.

### Voluntary Registration

Certain sections of Workman Publishing require that visitors register by providing an email address that is recorded in databases on our server. We do not collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without first obtaining verifiable parental consent, unless we only use such information to: (1) obtain parental consent or provide parents with notice; (2) respond directly on a one-time basis to a child's specific request; (3) respond more than once to a child's specific request along with providing parental notice of such use; (4) protect the safety of a child; or (5) comply with legal requirements. The consent and notification process mentioned above gives parents the ability to let us know if they do not want us to make further use of the personally identifiable information we have collected from their child.

Many of our contests are available only to those 18 years of age and above. Please read individual contest rules before entering.

We consider the following, among other things, to be personally identifiable information: first and last name, email address, street address and phone number. We may request such personally identifiable information from children in connection with our contests, sweepstakes, games, surveys, forums, subscription registrations, content submissions, classroom activities, requests for suggestions, and visitors' requests for free products, services (such as our magazines) or additional information, so that we can contact a winner, answer questions or requests, and fulfill orders.

Unless we indicate otherwise, personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 will be used solely by Workman Publishing.

Volunteered information is kept strictly confidential. Workman Publishing does not share or sell personally identifiable information to other companies. However, information that is voluntarily provided may be used internally, for example, to send email announcements of events on the site to users who registered for similar events and for direct mailings to the readers of Workman Publishing. Additionally, Workman Publishing may choose, on occasion, to include third-party offers in our mailings. We maintain appropriate and reasonable safeguards to ensure the integrity, security, and privacy of the information in our possession.

You may opt not to be included in the email announcements or mailings when you register for one of our offerings. If a particular registration form does not have this option, or, if you'd like to be removed from our lists for any reason, notify Workman directly by emailing info@workman.com. Please include your name, email address, and the offer for which you were registered so that we can effectively remove you from the database.

### For Kids

Remember to be smart online. Do not give out your full name, email address, home address, telephone number or any other personal information that would enable someone to contact you either online or offline, without first asking your parent or guardian for permission. Sometimes on our site we will ask you for your first name and email address along with your parents' email or home address. We do this so that we can contact your parents to let them know that you have communicated with us, and that we have collected this information from you.

### For Parents

There are many activities on Workman Publishing sites that children can participate in and enjoy without having to share personally identifiable information.

For those activities that require personally identifiable information, such as contests and sweepstakes (in compliance with the Federal Trade Commission's Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), Workman Publishing will not condition a child's participation in an activity on that child disclosing more personally identifiable information than is reasonably necessary to administer the activity. For certain online activities, we require verifiable parental consent before collecting or using a child's personally identifiable information. With these activities, Workman Publishing will notify the respective parent of our privacy policy and obtain verifiable parental consent before collecting personally identifiable information from a child.

Parents can request to review or have deleted their child's personally identifiable information from Workman Publishing's records, and refuse to permit further use of a child's information by contacting us at info@workman.com.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of information that a Web server asks your browser to store on the hard drive of your computer. Your browser later presents the information back to the Web server. In its simplest form, a cookie is just an identifying number.

### Bookstore Sites

Workman Publishing provides links to online bookstores and other retailers who may collect information from customers and share that information with Workman Publishing. Workman Publishing may use this information for marketing or research purposes, but will not disclose this information to third parties.

### Links to Other Sites

This site may be linked to sites that are not operated by Workman Publishing or any company affiliated with Workman Publishing. Workman Publishing is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these third party sites. This site may also be linked to Websites operated by companies affiliated with Workman Publishing. Visitors to those sites should refer to their separate privacy policies and practices.

### Contests and Promotions

Workman Publishing may run contests and promotions on our sites that may require the submission of personal information by participants. Workman Publishing may use the information collected during a contest for research purposes, for example, to determine how many visitors participated in the contest.

### Comments, Ideas, and Suggestions

Workman Publishing may obtain information from a user when a comment is mailed to or posted on our site by that user. We use this information only for the purpose for which it was submitted and will not share this information with any third parties. Any comments, ideas, or suggestions submitted to Workman's sites or directly to Workman Publishing become the property of Workman Publishing and may be used by Workman Publishing in print, including but not limited to books, newsletters, and Websites.

When visitors to sites owned and/or created by Workman Publishing voluntarily disclose personal information (user name, email address. etc.) on the bulletin boards or in chat areas, that information becomes public and can be collected and used by others, which may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or parties.
